Guide to the The Sherwoods records, 1957-1973.
Sherwoods records, The
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The Sherwoods records, 1957-1973.
37-6-4310
The Sherwoods.
1 cubic feet.
Documents, recordings
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records include photographs, correspondence, travel documentation, publicity and flyers, two phonograph records and a CD.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Sherwoods were a Glee Club spinoff a cappella group formed in 1956.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records include photographs, correspondence, travel documentation, publicity and flyers, two phonograph records and a CD.
SUBJECTS
Names:
The Sherwoods.; Cornell University. Glee Club.; Cornell University -- Students.
Subjects:
A cappella.. .
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Travel Correspondence and Planning Notes
Series II. Publicity
Series III. Cornell University Activities
Series IV. Performances
Series V. Audio Material
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Travel Correspondence and Planning Notes
  - Trip Correspondence (Old) - Ski Lodges - Castle Harbour Hotel, Bermuda, Mar 1957 - Apr 1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Vacation - Correspondence and Planning Notes, July 1959 - Dec 1959, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Half Moon Hotel, Aug 1959 - Sept 1961, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes lyrics of a song; itinerary; expense tabs
  - Spring Tour 1964, 1963-01-1964-01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Trip 1965 - Caneel Bay Plantation, 1964-11-1965-03 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Hotel Correspondence (1 of 5), Mar 1957 - Jan 1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Newspaper clippings of cruise advertisements
  - Assorted Hotel Correspondence (2 of 5), Mar 1957 - May 1958, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Handwritten planning notes; correspondence for 1958 trip; hotel newspaper advertisement
  - Assorted Hotel Correspondence (3 of 5), July - Sept 1959, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Poster titled "Hotel Continental at New York International Airport" with a note handwritten on the back to possibly a member of the Sherwoods
  - Assorted Hotel Correspondence (4 of 5), 1964-1967, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Mailed letters; newspaper clippings of hotel advertisements; a map of New Jersey; a map of Aspen, Colorado
  - Assorted Hotel Correspondence (5 of 5), 1971-1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Receipt for printing service; handwritten correspondence
  - Expenses, 1966-1967, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brochures, 1963, 1971, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Series II. Publicity, 1959-1972
  - Publicity, 1959-1965, 1971-1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Flyers; performance programs; flyer/poster/logo designs; flyer draft; correspondence; newsletters; record publicity
  - Hotel Correspondence, 1960-1961, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Flyers of Other Singing Groups, 1964-1967, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Flyer and Poster Design Layouts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Series III. Cornell University Activities, 1956-1973
  - Cornell University Activities, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Includes booklet of Cornell songs; flyers of the Sherwoods; flyer for auditions and try-out form; pamphlet of the Cornell University Glee Club; Policies and Regulations on Student Conduct; Policies and Procedures Affecting Student Organizations
  - Fall Tonic Concert, 1965-1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Correspondence; expenses and revenues
  - General Correspondence, 1956-1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - James H. Hood File, 1972-1973, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Copies of song lyrics/poetry; correspondence; empty envelope with a written note on the back
- Series IV. Performances, 1956-1972
  - Performance Requests and Payments (1 of 3), 1956-11-1961-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Handwritten cards and typed correspondence
  - Performance Requests and Payments (2 of 3), 1957-1971, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Performance Requests and Payments (3 of 3), 1971-1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Request to included in 1972 Cornellian Yearbook; draft of Fall Tonic concert flyer; receipts
  - Robert L. Maxwell - Artist Representative, Correspondence, 1959-04-1966-02 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Collegiate Sound Productions, Nov 1964 - Apr 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Correspondence; program; newspaper advertisement; handwritten planning notes
  - Reunion, 1959-1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Correspondence and lists
  - Performances at Girls Schools, Oct-Dec 1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Newspaper clipping advertisement; Russell Sage College newsletter
- Series VI. Audio Material
  - Try to Remember: The Reunion Album, Vol. 1, Undated; CD-5145 (Box 1)
  - What's All This Noise, Undated; SR-31465
  - Sherwood's at Zinck's, Undated; SR-31466